{
    "subject": "resource/On\u00e1n_Barreiros",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "Spain",
    "human_readable": "On\u00e1n Barreiros was born in Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864441752433777,
            "question": "Is Spain the birthplace of On\u00e1n Barreiros?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9367934465408325,
            "question": "Where was On\u00e1n Barreiros born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8511633276939392,
            "question": "Is On\u00e1n Barreiros Spanish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8136290311813354,
            "question": "What country is associated with On\u00e1n Barreiros' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7893493175506592,
            "question": "In which country did On\u00e1n Barreiros come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7804625630378723,
            "question": "Where was On\u00e1n Barreiros from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7652195692062378,
            "question": "What nationality is On\u00e1n Barreiros?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7543916702270508,
            "question": "Who is On\u00e1n Barreiros?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5328903794288635,
            "question": "What is known about On\u00e1n Barreiros' origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40465155243873596,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about On\u00e1n Barreiros?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On\u00e1n Barreiros was born in Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1093_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about On\u00e1n Barreiros' origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1093_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is On\u00e1n Barreiros?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1093_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is On\u00e1n Barreiros?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1093_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1093_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the answer to your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents mention that On\u00e1n Barreiros was born in Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Gran Canaria, Canary Islands, Spain. This information supports the triple statement that On\u00e1n Barreiros was born in Spain."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"On\u00e1n Barreiros was born in Spain.\" Specifically, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1093/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt` states: \"On\u00e1n Barreiros was born on 3 November 1981 in Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Gran Canaria, Canary Islands, Spain.\" This confirms his birthplace as being within Spain."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}